




const questions = [
    {
      question: "'Red Skies' and 'Saved by Zero' were huge hits for which 80,s band ?",
      options: ["Flock of Seagulls", "The Fixx", "Duran Duran", "Depeche Mode"],
      answer: "The Fixx",
     audioSrc: "https://youtu.be/pIe-Cj071l0?t=2",
      
    },
    {
      question: "Who's alter-ego was Ziggy Stardust'?",
      options: ["Iggy Pop", "Alice Cooper", "Lou Reed", "David Bowie"],
      answer: "David Bowie"
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the original guitarist for Led Zeppellin?" ,
      options: ["Peter Frampton", "Jeff Beck", "Larry Carlton" , "Jimmy Page"],
      answer: "Jimmy Page"
    },
    {
      question: 'Who wrote the song "I shot the Sherriff"?',
      options: ["Eric Clapton", "Leon Russell", "Bob Marley", "Steel Pulse"],
      answer: "Bob Marley"
    },
    {
      question: "Should I Stay or Should I go was a huge hit for which band?",
      options: ["The Ramones", "Velvet Underground", "The Sex Pistols", "The Clash"],
      answer: "The Clash"
    },
    {
      question: '"Sweetest Tabboo" and "Smooth Operator" were huge hits for which singer',
      options: ["Tina Marie", "Whitney Houston", "Sade", "Anita Baker"],
      answer: "Sade"
    },
    {
      question: 'Who wrote the jazz standard" So What?',
      options: ["John Coltrane", "Wes Montgomery", "Thelonius Monk", "Miles Davis"],
      answer: "Miles Davis"
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was dubbed "The Queen of Salsa"?',
      options: ["Celia Cruz", "Olga Guillot", "Lola Flores", "La Lupe"],
      answer: "Celia Cruz"
    },
    {
      question: 'The show "Bad Boys" had people singing the theme song . What was the name of this band ?',
      options: ["UB40", "Inner Circle", "Third World", "Aswad"],
      answer: "Inner Circle"
    },
    {
      question: '"Birdland" was a huge hit for this jazz Giant in 1971',
      options: ["Charlie Parker", "Glen Miller", "Tower of Power", "Weather Report"],
      answer: "Weather Report"
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the singer for the band Thin Lizzy",
      options: ["Sting", "Phil Lynott", "Steve Perry", "Rick Emmett"],
      answer: "Phil Lynott"
    },
    {
      question: "Who was known as the 'Old Blue Eyes'?",
      options: ["Frank Sinatra", "David Coverdale", "Andy Williams", "Perry Como"],
      answer: "Frank Sinatra"
    },
    {
      question: "Moonglow was a big hit in 1936 for this band leader ?",
      options: ["Artie Shaw", "Tommy Dorsey", "Dave Brubeck", "Benny Goodman"],
      answer: "Benny Goodman"
    },
    {
      question: '"Breezin was a huge hit for this great guitrist"',
      options: ["Eddie Van Halen", "Mateo Mancusso", "Carlos Santana", "George Benson"],
      answer: "George Benson"
    },
    {
    
      question: "What year did the Beatles play on'Ed Sullivan' ?",
      options: ["1960", "1970", "1964", "1972"],
      answer: "1964"
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the original singer for Genesis?",
      options: ["David Vedder", "Phil Collins", "Billy Squire", "Peter Gabriel"],
      answer: "Peter Gabriel"
    },
    {
      question: "Maybe the greatest rock guitar solos ever. Who was the guitarist on 'Eruption'?",
      options: ["Jimi Hendrix", "Steve Vai", "Joe Satriani", "Eddie Van Halen"],
      answer: "Eddie Van Halen"
    },
    {
      question: "The song,'Bamboleo' went mainstream for this Rumba Flamenca band'?",
      options: ["Los Del Rio", "Gypsy Kings", "Gente De Zona", "Habana de Primera"],
      answer: "Gypsy Kings"
    },
    {
      question: "Arguably the greatest Flamenco guitarist ever.Who wrote and plaed the orinal song 'Entre Dos Aguas'?",
      options: ["Diego del Morao", "Tomatito", "Paco De Lucia", "Sabicas"],
      answer: "Paco De Lucia"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these songs is not by Lynard Skynard'?",
      options: ["Sweet Home Alabama", "Mississippi Queen", "Tuesday's Gone", "Mr.Saturday Night"],
      answer: "Mississippi Queen"
    },
    {
      question: "The orangutang in the Jungle Book sings 'I wanna be like you'Who is the vice behind the primate?'",
      options: ["Dean Martin", "Bing Crosby", "Louie Prima ", "Bobby Darin"],
      answer: "Louie Prima "
    },
    {
      question: "What year wasthe Pink Floyd album'Dark Side of the Moon' released'?",
      options: ["1973", "1969", "1978", "1982"],
      answer: "1973"
    },
    {
      question: "who was Garfunkel's singing partner?",
      options: ["Garfinkle ", "Patsy Cline", "Simon", "Garfield"],
      answer: "Simon"
    },
    {
      question: "Geddy Lee was the lead singer which famous rock band?",
      options: ["King Crimson", "Rush", "Triumph", "Boston"],
      answer: "Rush"
    },
    {

      question: "in this song by Eddie Money. how many tickets does he have to Paradise?",
      options: ["1", "8", "2", "3"],
      answer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is Jane through with in this 1988 hit by Jane's Addiction'?",
      options: ["Romeo", "Everybody","Sergio", "Cameo's"],
      answer: "Sergio"
    },
    {
      question: "In 1974 Led Zeppelin decided to launch thei own record label. What was its name?",
      options: ["Led Balloon", "Cosmic", "Satellite", "Swan Song"],
      answer: "Swan Song"
    },
    {
      question: "This all female rock band had a big hit with the song 'What's Up'.What is the name of this band?",
      options: ["The Go-Go's", "The Vandals", "the Bangles", "4 Non Blondes"],
      answer: "4 Non Blondes"
    },
    {
      question: "Which band released 'Hard to Handle' in 1990?",
      options: ["Nirvana", "Rage Against the Machine", "Black Crowes", "Molly Hatchet"],
      answer: "Black Crowes"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the lead singer for Pearl Jam'?",
      options: ["Perry Comoy", "Eddie Vedder", "Dave Grohl", "Michael Stipe"],
      answer: "Eddie Vedder"
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the drummer for the band , The Police?",
      options: ["Dave Grohl", "Stewart Copeland", "John Bonham", "Neil Pert"],
      answer: "Stewart Copeland"
    },
    {
      question: "'Reasons' was a huge hit for this band in the early 70's'?",
      options: ["Parliament", "Kool and the Gang", "Earth Wind and Fire", "The O'jays"],
      answer: "Earth Wind and Fire"
    },










    

    
    // Add more questions here
  ];
  
  let currentQuestionIndex = 0;
  let score = 0;
  
  const questionElement = document.getElementById('question');
  const optionsElement = document.getElementById('options');
  const scoreElement = document.getElementById('score');
  const playButton = document.getElementById('play-song');
  const audio = document.getElementById('audio');
  const audioSource = document.getElementById('audio-source');

  function displayQuestion() {
    const currentQuestion = questions[currentQuestionIndex];
    questionElement.textContent = currentQuestion.question;
  
    optionsElement.innerHTML = '';
    currentQuestion.options.forEach(option => {
      const li = document.createElement('li');
      li.textContent = option;
      li.addEventListener('click', () => checkAnswer(option));
      optionsElement.appendChild(li);
    });
  }
  
  function checkAnswer(selectedOption) {
    const currentQuestion = questions[currentQuestionIndex];
    if (selectedOption === currentQuestion.answer) {
      score++;
      scoreElement.textContent = score;
      playAudio(audioSource);
    }
    currentQuestionIndex++;
    if (currentQuestionIndex < questions.length) {
      displayQuestion();
    } else {
      alert('Game Over! Your final score is ' + score);
    }
  }

  function playAudio(audioSrc) {
audioSource.src = audioSrc;
audio.load();
audio.play();
  }

  document.getElementById('next-button').addEventListener('click', () => {
    if (currentQuestionIndex < questions.length) {
      displayQuestion();
    }
  });
  
  
  
  document.getElementById('start-over').addEventListener('click',() => {
    startOver();
  });
  
  function startOver() {
    currentQuestionIndex = 0;
    score = 0;
    displayQuestion();
  }
  displayQuestion();
  